NYS PERB Agreements 5140
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Fire and Police: Rome through St. Paul (Box 299)
  - Sag - Harbor, 1975-1987 (Box 299, Folder 15)
  - Sag Harbor, 1987-1991 (Box 299, Folder 16)
  - St. Lawrence (Co.), 1978-1979 (Box 299, Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence (countries), 1998-2002 (Box 299, Folder 18)
  - St. Paul Blvd. Prof. Firefighters (Rochester), 1974-2000 (Box 299, Folder 19)
  - St. Paul Boulevard Fire District, 2000-2003 (Box 299, Folder 20)
  - Saint Paul Boulevard, 1989-1991 (Box 299, Folder 21)
- Fire and Police: Salamanca through Suaugerties (Box 300)
  - Salamanca (Police + Firemen), 1978-1988 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Salamanca (Police + Firemen), 1978-1983 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Salamanca (cities), 1996-1999 (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - Sands Point (Police), 1977-1982 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - Sands Point (Firefighters), 1973-1980 (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - Sands Point (Village), 1992-1995 (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - Sands Point, 1986-1991 (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - Saranac Lake, 1990-1996 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - Saranac Lake (Firefighters), 1971-1972 (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - Saranac Lake (Police), 1979-1986 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga (countries), 1997-2002 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - Saratoga Springs, City of (Police), 1976-1999 (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - Saratoga Springs, 1989-1995 (Box 300, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga Springs (cities), 1993-2003 (Box 300, Folder 14)
  - Saratoga County, 1984-1996 (Box 300, Folder 15)
  - Saugerties, 1975-1992 (Box 300, Folder 16)
  - Saugerties - Village, 1999-2001 (Box 300, Folder 17)
- Fire and Police: Scarsdale through Sidney (Box 301)
  - Scarsdale (Firemen), 1974-1979 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Scarsdale (Police), 1974-1980 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Scarsdale, 1990-1996 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady (cities), 1997-1999 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady (Police), 1968-1991 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady (Firemen), 1975-1978 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Schenectady (Police), 1975-1980 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady (Firemen), 1980-1992 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - Schenectady (Co), 1981-1992 (Box 301, Folder 9)
  - Schoharie (Countries), 1991-1993 (Box 301, Folder 10)
  - Schuyler County (Police), 1973-1982 (Box 301, Folder 11)
  - Scotia, Fire and Police Dept., 1970-1983 (Box 301, Folder 12)
  - Scotia, 1981-1989 (Box 301, Folder 13)
  - Seldon Fire District, 1998 (Box 301, Folder 14)
  - Seldon, 1978-1987 (Box 301, Folder 15)
  - Seneca County Police, 1986-1998 (Box 301, Folder 16)
  - Seneca Falls (Policemen), 1971-1976 (Box 301, Folder 17)
  - Seneca Falls (Police), 1976-1983 (Box 301, Folder 18)
  - Seneca Falls, 1987 (Box 301, Folder 19)
  - Town of Shawangunk, 1996-1999 (Box 301, Folder 20)
  - Shelter Island, 1999-2001 (Box 301, Folder 21)
  - Sherrill, 1988 (Box 301, Folder 22)
  - Sherrill, 1990-1992 (Box 301, Folder 23)
  - Sherrill (cities), 1996 (Box 301, Folder 24)
  - Sidney, 1979-1997 (Box 301, Folder 25)
- Fire and Police: Skaneateles through Suffern (Box 302)
  - Skaneateles, 1988-1996 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Sleepy Hollow - Village, 1999-2000 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Sloatsburg (village), 1986-1990 (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Solvay (Police), 1971-1982 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Solvay, 1987-1992 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - South Glens Falls, 1986-1992 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - South Glens Falls - Village, 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - South Nyack, 1981-1996 (Box 302, Folder 8)
  - South Nyack, 1973-1992 (Box 302, Folder 9)
  - South Glen Falls, village of (Police), 1974-1984 (Box 302, Folder 10)
  - Southampton (Police), 1979-1980 (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - Southampton Village Police Radio Operators, 1983-1985 (Box 302, Folder 12)
  - Southold (Police), 1971-1976 (Box 302, Folder 13)
  - Southold - towns, 2000-2002 (Box 302, Folder 14)
  - Spring Valley (Police), 1975-1984 (Box 302, Folder 15)
  - Spring Valley - Village, 1988-2001 (Box 302, Folder 16)
  - Springville, village of, 1977-1981 (Box 302, Folder 17)
  - Steuben, 1991 (Box 302, Folder 18)
  - Steuben (countries), 1993-2004 (Box 302, Folder 19)
  - Stony Point (Towns), 1986-1999 (Box 302, Folder 20)
  - Stony Point (Police), 1972-1989 (Box 302, Folder 21)
  - Suffern Village (Police), 1976-1986 (Box 302, Folder 22)
  - Suffern - Village (Police), 1978-1985 (Box 302, Folder 23)
  - Suffern, Patrolmen's Benevolent Ass'n., 1969-1972 (Box 302, Folder 24)
- Fire and Police: Suffolk through Syracuse (Box 303)
  - Suffolk County (Police), 1970-1988 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Suffolk County - Policemen, 1970-1971 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Suffolk (Co.), 1986-1988 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - Suffolk (Counties), 1992-1996 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Sullivan (Counties), 1997-1999 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, 1988-1993 (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - Syracuse (cities), 1993 (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse (Firemen), 1975-1982 (Box 303, Folder 8)
  - Syracuse (Firemen), 1971-1998 (Box 303, Folder 9)
  - Syracuse, 1987-1988 (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - Tacoma (Policemen), 1974 (Box 303, Folder 11)
- Fire and Police: Tarrytown through Troy (Box 304)
  - Torreytown (Policemen), 1963-1970 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Tioga, 1968-2001 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins, 1995-2000 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Tonawanda, City (Firemen), 1972-1974 (Box 304, Folder 4)
  - Tonawanda (Firemen), 1974-1976 (Box 304, Folder 5)
  - Tonawanda (Police), 1976-1993 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Tonawanda, 1989-1995 (Box 304, Folder 7)
  - Tonawanda, City (Police), 1972-1988 (Box 304, Folder 8)
  - Towanda (cities), 1994-1996 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Troy (Cities), 1994-1995 (Box 304, Folder 10)
  - Troy (Police), 1968-1990 (Box 304, Folder 11)
  - Troy (Firemen), 1983-1987 (Box 304, Folder 12)
- Fire and Police: Tuckahoe through Warwick (Box 305)
  - Tuckahoe, 1988-1990 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Tuckahoe - village, 1996 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Tuckahoe (Police), 1974 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - Ulster, 1979-1999 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Ulster (Co.), 1984-2003 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - Utica (Fire), 1974-1978 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Utica (cities), 1987-1992 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - Utica - Police, 1981-1983 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Utica (Firemen), 1973-1984 (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - Vestal, Town of (Police), 1969-1971 (Box 305, Folder 10)
  - Vestal (Towns), 1993-1994 (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Vestal (Police), 1975-1982 (Box 305, Folder 12)
  - Vestal, 1987-1989 (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Walden, 1975-1991 (Box 305, Folder 14)
  - Walden - Villages, 1993-1996 (Box 305, Folder 15)
  - Wallkill, 1995-1998 (Box 305, Folder 16)
  - Wallkill (Towns), 1992-1995 (Box 305, Folder 17)
  - Walton - villages, 1996-1999 (Box 305, Folder 18)
  - Waltons, 1987-1996 (Box 305, Folder 19)
  - Wappinger Falls (Village), 1994-2001 (Box 305, Folder 20)
  - Nappinger's Falls, 1977-2000 (Box 305, Folder 21)
  - Warren (countries), 1989-1995 (Box 305, Folder 22)
  - Warwick, 1971-1985 (Box 305, Folder 23)
  - Warwick, 1987-2002 (Box 305, Folder 24)
  - Warwick (Towns), 1996-1998 (Box 305, Folder 25)
  - Warwick - village, 1968-1971 (Box 305, Folder 26)
- Fire and Police: Washington through Wellsville (Box 306)
  - Washington Co., 1995-1996 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Washingtonville, 1973-1984 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Washingtonville, 1999-2003 (Box 306, Folder 3)
  - Waterford, 1991 (Box 306, Folder 4)
  - Waterford (Towns), 1994-1996 (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Waterloo, 1977-1987 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - Waterloo, 1988-1991 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - Waterloo - Village, 1998-2005 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - Watertown (Police + Firemen), 1968-1981 (Box 306, Folder 9)
  - Watertown (cities), 1992-1996 (Box 306, Folder 10)
  - Watertown, City of (Police + Firemen), 1968-1988 (Box 306, Folder 11)
  - Watertown, 1990 (Box 306, Folder 12)
  - Watervliet (Firemen), 1978-1989 (Box 306, Folder 13)
  - Watervliet (Police), 1970-1975 (Box 306, Folder 14)
  - Watervliet, City if (Firemen), 1968-1978 (Box 306, Folder 15)
  - Watkins Glen (Police), 1988-1989 (Box 306, Folder 16)
  - Watkins Glen - village, 1994 (Box 306, Folder 17)
  - Waverly, 1985-2000 (Box 306, Folder 18)
  - Waverly, 1989 (Box 306, Folder 19)
  - Wayne, 1989-1996 (Box 306, Folder 20)
  - Wayne - Countries, 1998-2000 (Box 306, Folder 21)
  - Wayne Co. of (Police), 1975-1994 (Box 306, Folder 22)
  - Webster (Police), 1972-1990 (Box 306, Folder 23)
  - Wellsville, 1977 (Box 306, Folder 24)
- Fire and Police: West Seneca through Woodridge (Box 307)
  - West Seneca (towns), 1992 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - West Seneca (Police), 1981-1987 (Box 307, Folder 2)
  - West Seneca, 1985-1991 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - West Seneca (Police), 1969-1974 (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Westchester (Police), 1969-1988 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - Westhampton, 1984-1989 (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - Westhampton, Village of (Police), 1977-1984 (Box 307, Folder 7)
  - Westhampton Beach (Police), 1973 (Box 307, Folder 8)
  - West Hampton Beach, 1986-1991 (Box 307, Folder 9)
  - Westhampton Beach, 1991-1994 (Box 307, Folder 10)
  - White Plains (cities), 1999-2002 (Box 307, Folder 11)
  - White Plains (Firemen), 1975-1977 (Box 307, Folder 12)
  - White Plains, Police, 1976-1983 (Box 307, Folder 13)
  - White Plains (Firemen), 1973 (Box 307, Folder 14)
  - White Plain (Firemen), 1987-1989 (Box 307, Folder 15)
  - White Plains (Police), 1970-1989 (Box 307, Folder 16)
  - White Plains, 1983-2000 (Box 307, Folder 17)
  - Woodbury (Towns), 1993-1994 (Box 307, Folder 18)
  - Woodbury, 1991 (Box 307, Folder 19)
  - Woodridge, 1999 (Box 307, Folder 20)
- Fire and Police: Yates through Yorktown (Box 308)
  - Yates, Co. of (Police), 1970-1971 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Yates - Countries, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Yates (Police), 1970-1985 (Box 308, Folder 3)
  - Yates, 1989-1994 (Box 308, Folder 4)
  - Yonkers, City of (Policemen) + (Firemen), 1969-1986 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - Yonkers, 1991-1993 (Box 308, Folder 6)
  - Yonkers (cities), 1993-1997 (Box 308, Folder 7)
  - Yorktown (Police), 1973-1982 (Box 308, Folder 8)
  - Yorktown (Towns), 1989-1990 (Box 308, Folder 9)
- Municipalities: Albany through Amherst (Box 309)
  - Albany, 1986-1990 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Albany, 1975-1986 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - Albion, 1974-1988 (Box 309, Folder 3)
  - Albion, 1991 (Box 309, Folder 4)
  - Albion (town), 1995-1996 (Box 309, Folder 5)
  - Albion - Village, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 6)
  - Alden, Town of, 1987-1996 (Box 309, Folder 7)
  - Alden Village of, 1989-1995 (Box 309, Folder 8)
  - Alexandria, 1987-1999 (Box 309, Folder 9)
  - Alfred, 1980-1985 (Box 309, Folder 10)
  - Alleghany, 2001-2003 (Box 309, Folder 11)
  - Autamont, 1996 (Box 309, Folder 12)
  - Amherst - Town, 1995-2000 (Box 309, Folder 13)
  - Amherst, 1995-1996 (Box 309, Folder 14)
  - Amherst, 1989-1992 (Box 309, Folder 15)
- Municipalities: Amherst through Arcade (Box 310)
  - Amherst, 1979-1994 (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - Amherst, 1982 (Box 310, Folder 2)
  - Amityville, 1984-1991 (Box 310, Folder 3)
  - Amityville, 1984-1994 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - Amsterdam, 1980-1998 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Amsterdam, 1990-1993 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - Amsterdam (Town), 1996 (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - City of Amsterdam, 1991-1999 (Box 310, Folder 8)
  - Andes, 1987 (Box 310, Folder 9)
  - Andes, 1981 (Box 310, Folder 10)
  - Andes (Town), 1997 (Box 310, Folder 11)
  - Andover (Town), 1991-1993 (Box 310, Folder 12)
  - Angola. Village of, 1976-1987 (Box 310, Folder 13)
  - Angola, Village of, 1976-1987 (Box 310, Folder 14)
  - Angola, Village of, 1974 (Box 310, Folder 15)
  - Village of Angola, 1994 (Box 310, Folder 16)
  - Antwerp, 1988-1991 (Box 310, Folder 17)
  - Village of Arcade, 1997 (Box 310, Folder 18)
  - Arcade, 1978-1993 (Box 310, Folder 19)
- Municipalities: Argyle through Bath (Box 311)
  - Argyle, 1988-1994 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Argyle (Town) (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Attica, 1986-1991 (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Auburn - Cities (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Auburn, 1968-1981 (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Auburn, 1970-1991 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - Attica (Village), 1992-1995 (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - Avon, 1982-1988 (Box 311, Folder 8)
  - Babylon, 1982-1992 (Box 311, Folder 9)
  - Babylon, Town of, 1982-1984 (Box 311, Folder 10)
  - Baldwin, 1990 (Box 311, Folder 11)
  - Baldwinsville, 1968 (Box 311, Folder 12)
  - Baldwinsville, 1994-1996 (Box 311, Folder 13)
  - Baldwinsville, 1978-1989 (Box 311, Folder 14)
  - Baldwinsville, 1989-1992 (Box 311, Folder 15)
  - Barre, Town of, 1968-1974 (Box 311, Folder 16)
  - Town of Batavia, 1989-1992 (Box 311, Folder 17)
  - Batavia, 1992-1997 (Box 311, Folder 18)
  - Bath (Village), 1986-2004 (Box 311, Folder 19)
  - Bath, 1970-1986 (Box 311, Folder 20)
- Municipalities: Beacon through Binghamton (Box 312)
  - Beacon, 1976-1999 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Bedford, and Teamsters #456, 1980-2001 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Bethel, Town of, 1989-1997 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Bethel, 1972-1994 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Batavia, 1969-1995 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem, 1989-2001 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Batavia, 1972-1991 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Batavia, 1989-1993 (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - Bedford, 1988-1991 (Box 312, Folder 9)
  - Big Flats, 1991-1996 (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Big Flats, 1974-1977 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - Big Flats, 1987 (Box 312, Folder 12)
  - Cities - Binghamton, 1983-1998 (Box 312, Folder 13)
  - Binghamton, 1968-1998 (Box 312, Folder 14)
- Municipalities: Binghamton through Brookshaven (Box 313)
  - Binghamton, 1986-1998 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Binghamton, 1980-1985 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Blasdell, 1973-1990 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Blooming Grove, 1990-1995 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Bombay (town), 1987-1994 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Brasher, Town of, 1973-1983 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Brasher, 1988-1993 (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Brentwood (Public Library), 1990-1996 (Box 313, Folder 8)
  - Briarcliff, 1969-1977 (Box 313, Folder 9)
  - Briarcliff Manor, 1979-1984 (Box 313, Folder 10)
  - Briarcliff Manor - Village, 1989-1993 (Box 313, Folder 11)
  - Brighton, Town of, 1979-1985 (Box 313, Folder 12)
  - Brighton, 1989-1990 (Box 313, Folder 13)
  - Bristol - Town, 1997-1999 (Box 313, Folder 14)
  - Broadalbin, 1991-1999 (Box 313, Folder 15)
  - Brockport, 1971-1997 (Box 313, Folder 16)
  - Brookhaven (Town of), 1968-1983 (Box 313, Folder 17)
  - Towns - Brookhaven, 1987-2001 (Box 313, Folder 18)
  - Brookhaven, 1983-1991 (Box 313, Folder 19)
- Municipalities: Broome through Buffalo (Box 314)
  - Broome, 1975-1994 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Brunswick, Town of, 1976-1992 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Brunswick, 1990-1991 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Buchanan, 1980-1994 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo, 1968-1984 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo CI, 1990-2002 (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo, 1972-1982 (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo, 1986-1996 (Box 314, Folder 8)
- Municipalities: Buffalo through Camillus (Box 315)
  - Briarcliff Manor, 1968-1989 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo, 1970-1992 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo, 1970-1982 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo, 1978-1984 (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo, 1983-1993 (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - Cairo, 1973-1978 (Box 315, Folder 6)
  - Calicoon, 1976-1992 (Box 315, Folder 7)
  - Calicoon (Town), 1993-1995 (Box 315, Folder 8)
  - Camillus (Town), 1992-1997 (Box 315, Folder 9)
  - Camillus, 1979-1987 (Box 315, Folder 10)
- Municipalities: Camillus through Charleston (Box 316)
  - Camillus, 1989-1990 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - Canajoharie, 1971-1990 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - Canandaigua, 1976-1982 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Canandaigua, 1990-1994 (Box 316, Folder 4)
  - Canandaigua, 1971-1979 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - Canastota, 1979-1995 (Box 316, Folder 6)
  - Canton, 1989-2002 (Box 316, Folder 7)
  - Canton, Village of, 1974-1999 (Box 316, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, 1982-1992 (Box 316, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, 1991-1993 (Box 316, Folder 10)
  - Carlisle, 1992-1999 (Box 316, Folder 11)
  - Carmel, 1998-2000 (Box 316, Folder 12)
  - Carthage/West Carthage, 1994-2000 (Box 316, Folder 13)
  - Catskill, Village of + AFSCME #968, 1972-1980 (Box 316, Folder 14)
  - Catskill, town of, 1974-1978 (Box 316, Folder 15)
  - Catskill, 1984-1996 (Box 316, Folder 16)
  - Cayuga, 1978 (Box 316, Folder 17)
  - Cedarhurst, 1970-1984 (Box 316, Folder 18)
  - Cedarhurst, 1977-1995 (Box 316, Folder 19)
  - Villages - Cedarhurst, 1995-1998 (Box 316, Folder 20)
  - Central Islip, 1994 (Box 316, Folder 21)
  - Charleston - town, 1999-2001 (Box 316, Folder 22)
  - Chatham, 1991-2000 (Box 316, Folder 23)
- Municipalities: Cheektowaga through Clarkstown (Box 317)
  - Cheektowaga - Town, 1992 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - Cheektowaga, 1975-1988 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - Cheektowaga, 1989-1990 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Chenango, 1978-1983 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - Chenango (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - Chenango - town, 1999-2001 (Box 317, Folder 6)
  - Chenango, Town of, 1980-1998 (Box 317, Folder 7)
  - Chester, 1993-1999 (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - Chester, 1976-1982 (Box 317, Folder 9)
  - Chester, 1973-1990 (Box 317, Folder 10)
  - Chili, 1989-2001 (Box 317, Folder 11)
  - Chittenango, Village of, 1982-2004 (Box 317, Folder 12)
  - Cicero, 1984-1994 (Box 317, Folder 13)
  - Chateauguay, 1989-1992 (Box 317, Folder 14)
  - Chatham, 1974-1992 (Box 317, Folder 15)
  - Clarence - town, 1996-1998 (Box 317, Folder 16)
  - Clarkstown, Town of, 1980-1983 (Box 317, Folder 17)
  - Clarkstown - Towns, 1990-1995 (Box 317, Folder 18)
  - Clarkstown, 1987-1989 (Box 317, Folder 19)
- Municipalities: Clifton through Cortland (Box 318)
  - Clifton (Town), 1988-1991 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Clifton Park (Town), 1992-1994 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Clifton (Town of), 1971-1985 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Clinton (Town), 1968-1995 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Clinton (Uniform Essex - Franklin), 1990-2000 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - Cohoes - Cities, 1987-1990 (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - Cohoes, 1982-1986 (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - Colonie, 1983-1997 (Box 318, Folder 8)
  - Colonie, 1983-2002 (Box 318, Folder 9)
  - Colton, Town of, 1976-1997 (Box 318, Folder 10)
  - Colton, 1978-1990 (Box 318, Folder 11)
  - Columbus, Town of, 1985 (Box 318, Folder 12)
  - Copaigue Memorial Library, 1976-1989 (Box 318, Folder 13)
  - Corning (City of), 1969-1975 (Box 318, Folder 14)
  - Corning - Cities, 1990-1993 (Box 318, Folder 15)
  - Corning, 1973-1975 (Box 318, Folder 16)
  - Cornwall, 1978-1990 (Box 318, Folder 17)
  - Cortland, 1987-1994 (Box 318, Folder 18)
  - Cortland, 1989-1992 (Box 318, Folder 19)
  - Cortland - City, 1996-1999 (Box 318, Folder 20)
- Municipalities: Cortlandt through Dunkirk (Box 319)
  - Cortland, 1974-1981 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Cortland - Towns, 1995-1996 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Coxsackle - villages, 2000-2003 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Groton-on-Hudson, Village of, 1975-1993 (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Groton-on-Hudson, 1970-1996 (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Groton on Hudson, 1989 (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Danby, 1976-1991 (Box 319, Folder 7)
  - Danemora, 1989-1995 (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Dansville, 1984-1994 (Box 319, Folder 9)
  - Dansville, 1988-1994 (Box 319, Folder 10)
  - Davenport, 1970-1984 (Box 319, Folder 11)
  - Davenport, 1989-1990 (Box 319, Folder 12)
  - Deer Park, 1983-1986 (Box 319, Folder 13)
  - DeKalb, 1988-1999 (Box 319, Folder 14)
  - Delhi, Village of, 1986-2002 (Box 319, Folder 15)
  - Denmark, Town, 1990-1991 (Box 319, Folder 16)
  - Depew, 1974-2001 (Box 319, Folder 17)
  - Depew, 1992 (Box 319, Folder 18)
  - Dick Inson, 1982-1999 (Box 319, Folder 19)
  - Dobbs Ferry, + Teamsters #456, 1980-1995 (Box 319, Folder 20)
  - Dolgeville (village), 1990-1991 (Box 319, Folder 21)
  - Dolgeville, 1977-1980 (Box 319, Folder 22)
  - Dover, 1993-1995 (Box 319, Folder 23)
  - Dresden, 1989-1997 (Box 319, Folder 24)
  - Duanesburg, 1978-1994 (Box 319, Folder 25)
  - Dunkirk, City of, 1969 (Box 319, Folder 26)
- Municipalities: Eastchester through Eden (Box 320)
  - Eastchester, Town of, 1968-1990 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Eastchester - Towns, 1992-2002 (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Eastchester, 1973-1988 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Easton, 1997-2002 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - East Aurora, 1982-1994 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - East Aurora, 1974-1976 (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - East Fishkill, 1985-1991 (Box 320, Folder 7)
  - East Greenbush, 1990-1994 (Box 320, Folder 8)
  - East Hampton, 1980-1986 (Box 320, Folder 9)
  - East Hudson Parkway, 1972-1979 (Box 320, Folder 10)
  - Cities - Elmira, 1990-1992 (Box 320, Folder 11)
  - Villages - Elmira Heights, 1993-1996 (Box 320, Folder 12)
  - Elmira Heights, 1985-1993 (Box 320, Folder 13)
  - Elmsford (Village), 1982-1985 (Box 320, Folder 14)
  - Elmsford, Village of, 1973-1980 (Box 320, Folder 15)
  - Endicott, 1971-1987 (Box 320, Folder 16)
  - Endicott, 1990-1994 (Box 320, Folder 17)
- Municipalities: Edwards through Endicott (Box 321)
  - Edwards, Town of, 1984-1990 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Edwards, 1989-1990 (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - Ellenburg, 1977 (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - Ellenville, 1986-1994 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Ellenville, 1989-1996 (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - Ellicott, 1972-1984 (Box 321, Folder 6)
  - Ellicott, 1988-1991 (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - Ellisburg, 1989-1995 (Box 321, Folder 8)
  - Elmira, 1972-1989 (Box 321, Folder 9)
  - Elmira, 1970-1984 (Box 321, Folder 10)
  - Cities - Elmira, 1990-1992 (Box 321, Folder 11)
  - Cities - Elmira, 1990-1992 (Box 321, Folder 12)
  - Villages - Elmira Heights, 1993-1996 (Box 321, Folder 13)
  - Elmira Heights, 1985-1993 (Box 321, Folder 14)
  - Elmsford (Village), 1982-1985 (Box 321, Folder 15)
  - Elmsford, Village of, 1973-1980 (Box 321, Folder 16)
  - Endicott, 1971-1987 (Box 321, Folder 17)
  - Endicott, 1990-1994 (Box 321, Folder 18)
- Municipalities: Ephratah through Franklin Square (Box 322)
  - Epharatah & Mohawk Valley, 1976-1981 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - Ephatah, 1989-1991 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - Erie, 1976-1978 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - Town of Evans and Evans Water Department Exp., 1975-1981 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Evans, 1983-1991 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - Endicott - Villages, 1995-1997 (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - Ephratah (Towns), 1994-1995 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - Town of Essex, 2000-2002 (Box 322, Folder 8)
  - Evans - Towns, 1998-2001 (Box 322, Folder 9)
  - Village of, 1984-1992 (Box 322, Folder 10)
  - Fallsburg, 1971-1978 (Box 322, Folder 11)
  - Fallsburg, 1987-1992 (Box 322, Folder 12)
  - Farmingdale, 1980-1990 (Box 322, Folder 13)
  - Farmingdale Public Library Assn., 1996-1997 (Box 322, Folder 14)
  - Finklesteim Memorial Library, 1988-1997 (Box 322, Folder 15)
  - Floral Park, 1967-1971 (Box 322, Folder 16)
  - Floral Park, 1986-1989 (Box 322, Folder 17)
  - Forestburgh, 1985-1994 (Box 322, Folder 18)
  - Fort Covington, 1992-1997 (Box 322, Folder 19)
  - Fort Edward - Village, 1994-1996 (Box 322, Folder 20)
  - Fowler, 1975-1989 (Box 322, Folder 21)
  - Frankfort, 1998-2002 (Box 322, Folder 22)
  - Frankfort, 1981-1988 (Box 322, Folder 23)
  - Franklin, 1987-1989 (Box 322, Folder 24)
  - Franklin Square, 1991-1998 (Box 322, Folder 25)
- Municipalities: Fredonia through Geddes (Box 323)
  - Fredonia, 1968-1998 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - Fredonia, 1985-1989 (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - Freeport (Village of), 1976-1997 (Box 323, Folder 3)
  - Fremont, 1971-1997 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - Fulton, City of, 1977-1991 (Box 323, Folder 5)
  - Galway, Town of, 1976-1999 (Box 323, Folder 6)
  - Garden City, 1969-1990 (Box 323, Folder 7)
  - Garden City, 1989-1990 (Box 323, Folder 8)
  - Geddes Garden City. Village of, 1970-1987 (Box 323, Folder 9)
  - Gates, 1988-2000 (Box 323, Folder 10)
  - Geddes, 1978-1992 (Box 323, Folder 11)
- Municipalities: Geneseo through Grand Island (Box 324)
  - Geneseo, 1988-1992 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - Geneseo (Village), 1997-2000 (Box 324, Folder 2)
  - Geneva - Cities, 1996-2006 (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - Geneva, 1969-1991 (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - Geneva, 1989-1998 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - Geneva - Municipal, 1980-1995 (Box 324, Folder 6)
  - Town of Ghent, 1998 (Box 324, Folder 7)
  - Ghent, 1980-1987 (Box 324, Folder 8)
  - German Flats, 1990 (Box 324, Folder 9)